Hey, my dad's invitation to the party got returned.
Grandpa Cotton Hill Hell USA?
Bobby, why'd you write this?
You know your grandpa lives in Houston?
Mom says he's the devil.
Peggy, how can you tell Bobby that?
I said evil Hank.
How you get devil from that is beyond me.
I don't want grandpa at my party.
The kids are already gonna hate me because you got the wrong kind of bean dip.
What's wrong with the bean dip?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with your grandpa?
He's got big plastic teeth.
He screams all the time.
His legs don't work.
Bobby, never make funny your grandpa's legs.
He lost his shins defending Texas in World War II.
Now, son, pick up that phone and invite your granddad to your birthday party.
Okay.
Hi, Grandpa.
Bobby, if you're gonna fake dial, you gotta hit more than three numbers.
Woo!
This thing is a hoof!
Uh, I got a splinter here.
Orange, you glad I didn't say banana?
Huh?
This party's boring.
Everybody hates you.
Why are you so pissed off for Piggy Hill?
Oh, nothing.
Just Hank's father.
He's driving in for the party.
Oh, Lord, that crazy Cotton Hill.
I heard after Hank's mother left Cotton, he married his 16-year-old nurse.
Dee Dee is 39, thank you very much.
Although parts of her are much younger.
Ooh, Piggy Hill.
Dad, I'm dying out there.
I blew up a balloon with my nose.
Nothing.
I did this thing.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Did you try burping the alphabet?
That's my clothes, Dad.
Hey, man, what are you talking about?
What are you talking about, man?
I tell you what, Fat Kid's always funny one, man.
There's a thing called John Candy, John Belushi, Knife and Pork, dug their grave, man.
Who wants a burger?
Well, I'll take that steak.
The hell you say?
Did you win World War II?
This ribeye is for my daddy.
Cotton's coming.
Whoa-ho, if I was you, Con, I'd am-scray before he gets here.
Yeah, if he finds out you're from Japan, you know.
How many times I tell you, stupid, I'm Le Ocean!
Uh, you?
Uh, Vee?
Happy birthday, Bobby!
Oh, Dad, you crazy son of a gun.
You really outdid yourself this time.
Well, you know me.
I'm larger than life.
Where are its legs?
What are you looking at, Moe?
A Japanese machine gun blew my shins off in WW2.
So what?
You like that horse, Bobby?
I love it, Grandpa!
Well, you can love it for four more hours.
It's a riddle.
All right, who wants the first ride?
Me!
Hey, Hank's wife.
Well, how long have you been here, Cotton?
I didn't notice you... Didi!
Come on out here and gab with Hank's wife.
Look at here, Hank.
What do you think of your mama's new tie ties?
Oh, she is not my mother.
Hell, we went to kindergarten together.
Hey, Hank.
Do you still like finger painting?
Everyone thinks your party's cool, Bobby.
I'm having fun.
Your wife divorced you.
Mr. Kahn, I'll have a Mai Tai.
What do you think?
I look for Hank?
Dad, this here is my new neighbor.
He's Japanese.
No, he ain't.
He's Laotian.
Thank you, Mr. Kahn.
All right, time to open my gift.
Whoa!
A super squirter!
A two-bar squirter!
There ain't no water at all, Mr. Khan!
It's a genuine Winchester 20-gauge shotgun!
You got a real gun!
And now Peggy Hill has a real gun.
Bobby, you are too young to own a firearm, honey.
Did you see that, Hank?
Tell your woman to give him back his gun!
His woman?
Oh, God.
I am my own woman, and don't you forget.
Oh, Peg, uh, that's just cowboy talk.
Come on.
Hey, let's go bust open that piñata.
Kill the boy!
Ooh, Bastard!
Bastard!
Come on, Bobby.
Hank, the boy can barely reach it.
Now, lower the piñata so he has a chance at it.
Come on.
Oh!
Crap it!
Feel it!
Ooh, Bastard!
Bastard!
Kill it, boy!
It must be made of kryptonite or something.
We're crying out loud!
Oh, good Lord Cotton!
You gave him a loaded shotgun?
Well, you don't give a toile without batteries.
Come and get your Tootsie Rolls!
Oh, I'm so sorry your grandpa ruined your birthday, son.
He didn't ruin it.
He made it fine.
Bobby, come on over here, boy.
Take off them pink love.
That's women's work.
Leave him alone.
He's a good helper.
Oh, whatever you say, Hillary.
Cotton, I'll do the dishes.
I like to.
Permission granted.
Put an apron over your new bosom, too.
Don't tell her, but I got them cheap.
Both lefties!
So, Bobby, what's it gonna do with your life?
I'm gonna be a prop comic.
I'm working on this bit where I stick a green bean up my nose.
Well, now that sounds promising.
Hank, Bobby and me have decided he's gonna stick vegetables up his nose.
He's not gonna take over the family gas station.
Dad, I don't work at a gas station.
I sell propane and propane accessories.
Don't sass me, boy!
You ain't too big for me to give you a licking!
Oh, dad, you old skunk.
Come on, grease monkey.
Let's tangle.
All right, Kyle.
Now, you are breaking my good dishes.
It's time for you to leave.
Come on.
I will fix you a to-go plate.
Don't worry about the horse.
If it comes back, we'll call the rental place.
Damn, won't start.
I guess I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, no, no, no.
Just pop the hood.
Hank can fix it in a minute.
Don't bother, Uncle Hank.
I can't hear the solenoid plunger.
You're going to need a new one.
Thanks a lot, girly.
But the truth is, you're a girl.
Hank, we'll have to wait till your gas station opens up in the morning.
I guess I'm staying over.
I wish you could, but we are all out of beds.
I don't need a bed.
I can sleep in a drawer after what they did to me overseas.
I could sleep on the couch, Mom.
Well, that'll be just fine.
Excuse me for just a second.
I do not want that ill-mannered foul mouth old man to spend another moment in my house.
Oh, you just don't understand him, Peg.
See, he's a big flamboyant character like a peacock.
That's why men love him.
But women don't like his style because you all are like the pee hen.
More subdued and drab.
You just cannot see your father for who he is.
Well, Bobby and I both want him to stay.
So that means you're out voted.
Oh, yeah?
Well, Luann hates him, too.
That means we're even.
Well, Jesus loves him, so I win.
Well, what does that have to do with... Hey, Dad, we'd love it if you stayed.
Well, all righty.
Bitty, we're bunking here tonight.
Mr. Khan, my bag!
What do you say I drive you to school today, Bobby?
Hey, you fix my car yet?
I just woke up.
Just what?
It's 7 a.m.
If you were in the army, you could have dug 10 graves by now.
I hope you're all hungry.
Good looking breakfast, Peg.
Yeah, I see bacon.
I see ham.
I see steak.
Sausage!
Where's my sausage?
There's no sausage!
Well, Cotton, you are welcome to march yourself down to the safeway, but I have to get ready for work.
See you, Bobby.
Woman works.
Man loses his sausage.
You know, Cotton, I'd love to debate this with you, but I am just a little too busy living here in the latter half of the 20th century.
Hey dad, if you want to drive Bobby to school, use my truck.
I'll go rig up your pedal extenders.
You're all skin and bones, girly.
Put some cornpone on them hips.
I don't want any grandpa hell.
Don't want to get fat.
That's not for you to worry about.
You will never know if you are attractive.
It's up to a man to tell you that.
You keep eating, and I'll tell you when to stop.
Touch me again and go be wearing that cornpone, old man.
Really?
Feisty!
You sure it's okay for me to be out of school today, Grandpa?
Well, yeah, it's a holiday, isn't it?
It's Angie Dickinson's birthday.
Now, why don't you order us some food?
Really?
Dad never lets me order.
Yeah, well, you went with your daddy today.
Go to it.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Uh, ma'am.
Oh, good.
Sweet.
You'll never get no service that way.
You gotta get her in the moneymaker.
Hey, Missy.
How about some sandwiches?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Well, that's the dangedest thing.
I never heard of a solenoid just disappearing before.
I don't know.
Sometimes things just disappear for no logical reason.
One day my cousin woke up, his kidney was gone.
At the same time, five hundred miles away, a woman in Phoenix contracted diabetes.
I fixed it, Uncle Hank.
Oh, he purrs.
He's like, dang, old kid.
Yep, my dad sure knows how to take care of his cars.
When I was a baby, he had my mama make me a shammy jumpsuit, and I used to crawl around on the hood and buff it till it shined like Christmas.
Your dad, I swear.
How about when he took us down to the hotel, Arlen?
Oh, yeah.
Remember that, Hank?
Hank, you won the big game.
So, I'm buying you and your friends hookers.
Now come on, boys, pickers out that'll have one.
Hey there, Mr. Quarterback.
Not every dad would do something like that to his son.
I mean, for his son.
What, how's it coming with the car, grease monkey?
That's real funny, Peg.
Look what I found.
Wait, that's a solenoid.
Where'd you find that?
In Cotton's room, wrapped in his little bitty pants under a big pile of lies.
Damn it, I killed a whole day fixing that car.
I don't understand.
Oh, Hank, what is to understand?
Your father disfigured his own automobile just so he could stay here and drive me crazy.
Oh, Peggy, the poor guy just wants to spend time with us.
And you've made it so hard for him, he's afraid to ask.
You're right.
It's my fault.
Why didn't I serve that poor man his sausage?
What's the point in arguing?
The car is fixed now.
He'll be out of here tonight.
Aunt Peg, I found this timing belt in the laundry.
You want me to wash it with the darks?
Good morning, angels.
Do I have an assignment for you?
Good morning, Charlie.
Ah, damn!
It's a Shelley hack!
That's like getting a shimp.
What in the hell is going on here?
Where are your pants?
We were hot.
Take them off.
A man doesn't have to wear pants around the house if he doesn't want to.
Yeah, what you got them blue jeans on for, Hank?
Let's go.
Take them off.
I don't want to take them off.
Buddy, take your daddy's pants off.
Okie dokie cotton, Hank.
Fix your car.
I guess you'll be wanting to head back right about now.
Peggy.
Well, um, maybe we should think about getting back.
Huh, honey?
What did you say?
OK.
Now, what did you say, baby kinks?
We can leave.
Hank fixed the car.
Actually, Luann fixed it.
Oh, that's a good one, Hank's wife.
A woman fixing a car.
That's like a pig trying to read.
Yeah.
Well, I guess you can go home now, Dad.
Now, I don't think so.
We're gonna stick around a few more days.
Supper time, Colonel.
You've forgotten my beer!
Come on, get me my beer, woman.
Mom, I'll take my dinner in here, too.
Bobby, you will not.
We eat our dinner in the kitchen.
Boy wants his dinner in here.
Well, we eat in the kitchen.
Here.
Kitchen.
I forgot, psych, I need a little support here.
Well, Peggy, it might be nice for a change to have dinner in front of the TV.
Well, go on, woman, get me my dinner.
I don't know where you got the idea.
You could slap your mother's behind.
I'll tell you where he got the idea.
Your father.
And it's all your fault for not nipping it in the bud.
What do you want me to do?
I can't change my father.
Well, he certainly won't listen to me now, will he?
You're both men.
You're both peacocks, remember?
What are you turning into some kind of feminist?
I am not a feminist, Hank.
I am Peggy Hill, a citizen of the Republic of Texas.
I work hard, I sweat hard, and I love hard, and I gotta smell good and look pretty while I'm doing it.
So I comb my hair, I reapply lipstick 30 times a day, I do your dishes, I wash your clothes, and I clean the house.
Not because I have to, Hank, but because of a mutual unspoken agreement that I have never brought up because I am too much of a lady.
30 times a day?
Yeah, I'm kind of like it here.
What kind of work can that guy get in this town?
Uh, are you allergic to asbestos?
Hello?
Hey, Dad.
Hey, if it ain't the ol' grease monkey!
All right, Dad.
I need to talk to you about some of the things you've been telling Bobby.
I've been telling Bobby a lot of things.
For example, I told him how I lost my shins defending our country.
You want to hear that story, Fatty?
Sure, yes, sir!
Bill, I'm trying to talk to my... I was 14.
Just a little older than Bobby.
But I knew Uncle Sam needed me.
So I lied and signed up.
And we had beaten the Nazis in Italy.
And they shipped us to the Pacific Theater.
A Tojo torpedo sent our troops ship to the bottom.
I could only save three of my buddies.
Fatty, Stinky, and Brooklyn.
They were kind of like you fellas, only one of them was from Brooklyn.
Out of the sun came a Tojo Zero and put fifty bullets in my bow.
The blood attracted sharks.
I had to give them Fatty.
Then things took a turn for the worse.
I met it to an island.
But it was full of tojos.
They were spittin' on the US flag.
So I rushed them.
But it was a trap.
They opened fire and blew my skin off.
Last thing I remember, I beat them all to death with a big piece of fattie.
I woke up in a field hospital, and they were sewing my feet to my knees.
Now,
What was it you wanted to talk to me about, Hank?
Well, nothing, I guess.
You've had enough cake, Connie.
What are you doing?
A man's gotta tell a woman when to stop eating.
You're looking kind of chunky.
Oh, she's moody.
Must be PBS.
Let's go.
I gotta see a man about a horse.
Bobby, don't forget to bust your tray.
Ah, that's women's work.
Ain't that right, fellas?
Women's work!
Well, she's got a point, but he's a war hero.
She's my wife.
But he's got no shins.
Uh, I'm just trying to get a little propane here.
Stricklin' propane.
Bobby was sent home from school for starting a sexist riot today.
What?
I'm coming home right now.
Well, you're just a little too late, because the devil took Bobby off to the Hotel Arlen.
Hotel Arlen!
Bobby!
I'm proud of you for what you did at school today.
So I'm buying you a hooker.
Go ahead, pick yourself out alive way.
Alive one what?
Hey, cutie, you got papers?
Bobby, get over here now.
Grandpa said I could- Bobby, you heard your mother.
Get over there.
What are you saying, Hank?
Are you siding with your woman?
Look at me, son!
Look at my shins!
Look, Dad, I'm sorry about fatty and your shins, but I'm not a kid anymore.
Bobby is my boy, and I won't let him grow up to be a woman hating old fool.
No wonder Mom left you.
She was a strong lady, classy and smart like Peg.
Maybe you couldn't handle that, but I can.
My marriage is a partnership of equals.
Peggy might do all the housework, but there are a lot of other things that I'm supposed to do, but I'm not going to say what they are because I'm a gentleman.
Oh, I get it.
She's making you say this.
You're just her puppet.
No, Dad, I'm saying all this because I mean it.
Now, Dee Dee's out in the car.
I had her pack up.
It's time for you to head home.
Well, I never thought I'd see the day when my own son would stop loving me.
It's about time!
Love for sissies!
Ain't that right, ya house full of hookers?
All right, hookers, listen up.
I'll be back next year so don't be jacking up your prices.
I'll be staying over to Hank Hill's home.
Bobby, you gotta try and forget all that gobbledygook your grandpa told ya.
You listen to your mother, she knows best.
But she's a woman.
How could she know better than Grandpa?
Well, because she's a lot smarter than him for one, your mother's probably got a better head on her shoulders than anybody in Ireland.
Better than Bill, or Dale, or Boomerower?
Geez, Bobby, why not compare it to a baboon in the zoo?
But I thought they were your best friends.
Peggy's my best friend, son.
Mom?
That's right.
And when you're older, I hope you're lucky enough to find a girl to be best friends with, too.
You think that'll really happen to me?
Well, it won't if you keep slapping them in the butt and ordering them around.
You'll do okay.
You just have to remember one thing.
Women were not put on this earth to serve you and me.
Now, what do you say we get an ice cream?