Just two more.
Come on.
Okay.
Five more.
Hey, you said two.
You can't predict this tape.
I've done it enough to know.
My Game Boy's out of batteries.
I need to get on the Nintendo.
Quick!
Just a minute, Bobby.
Get ready to turn and turn.
Way to go, Bobby.
Hi, Uncle Hank.
Uh, shut that off.
Bobby, stop dancing now.
He is not just dancing.
He's firming his thighs and tightening his buttocks.
Watch your mouth.
Jesus.
Ah!
Jack!
Lou Anne!
Ah, damn it.
Ah, look at this place.
What is it, Uncle Hank?
The sofa beds in the out position.
And I can't find nothing in here anymore.
What are you looking for?
I didn't used to have to be looking for something.
I'd come into my den and just look.
Look at my different stuff and get ideas about what I want.
Don't worry, Uncle Hank.
I'll be out of your hair soon.
I think Buckley's gonna ask me to move in.
Isn't it neat?
I'll be going from daddy to you to Buckley.
Yeah, it's an amazing journey, Lou Ann.
What about this?
Maybe you want this record?
No, it doesn't work like that.
How about this tackle box?
Luanne, what did I just... Well, that might need reorganizing.
Why do you let Luan go out with that hairball?
It's none of my business.
She's not my daughter.
Anyway, that Buckley may be dumb as dirt, but he's her ticket out of my house.
Keep going!
They should be out of my sight by now.
And, man, in Dangle Birds, man, flying low this season, man, it's probably a dangle awkward, man, to take a look.
What the hell was that?
That was a breakup.
At least that's what it was the last time I ran into the house crying.
A lot of tears.
Guess what was on sale?
Oh, my lord, you've been dumped.
Oh, there, there.
All right, you tell Aunt Peggy all about it.
Fish sticks?
Oh.
Hey, you know, I was almost killed at this point.
Okay, Hank, please.
Try and be sensitive.
Okay, honey.
Go ahead, you let it out.
It is natural.
This is the healing process.
Peggy.
I had a talk with her today.
We are past the first hump, so that leaves only seven more humps.
Peggy, I need you to fix her now.
Without my quiet time, I'm not an effective propane salesman.
Well, you can't rush it, Hank.
The formula is, for however long she was dating him, that's how long it takes to get over him.
You mean we got three more weeks of this?
If you don't fix her, I'll have to.
Well, honey, I don't think you have the tools for that job.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, remember when my aunt died and you kept grabbing me around the waist and saying, let's wrestle.
Yeah, but you told me that helped you.
I did.
Well, yes, it did.
See?
Look, if you really want to help, sometime tomorrow you tell Louie and she looks pretty.
What's that got to do with anything?
She just needs to hear it from a man.
Three words, you look pretty and nothing more.
So whatcha thinkin' about there, Stu?
I'm thinkin' about flippin' that steak there.
Well, ratty.
No!
Flip that other one!
Don't go away.
We'll be right back with more of Make a Steak.
How you doin' out there?
I'm Chuck Manjoni.
You know, even celebrities have to hunt for bargains.
That's why I go to the Megalomark, where shopping feels so good.
This week, twelve five pound bags of gourmet chocolates for ten dollars.
That's Buckley's section.
You look pretty.
I was dumped.
Three words, nothing more.
You look pretty.
Nothing more.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I never liked that Buckley.
You should be happy.
That guy was an annoying greasy headed loser.
I was dumped by a loser.
Ah, jeez.
Luanne, sometimes life throws you a curveball.
Now there's two ways you can deal with it.
You can cry, and that's the path you've chosen, or you can not cry.
How do you not cry?
Well, instead of letting it out, try holding it in.
Every time you have a feeling, just stick it into a little pit inside your stomach and never let it out.
Are you supposed to have a pain under your rib?
Yes.
That's natural.
The body doesn't want to swallow its emotions.
But now you go ahead and put that pain inside your stomach, too.
I think it's working, Uncle Hank.
I feel sick, but not sad.
There you go.
Look at my friend Bill.
He went through the worst divorce this county's ever seen, but you never see him crying.
I'm scared I'll never find another guy.
Ah, don't worry about that.
Peggy told me.
If you dated your old boyfriend for three weeks, you'll get a new one in three weeks.
Tops.
Another thing I hate about Buckley, he always takes me to all you can eat and says that I have to sneak off his plate so I just get iced tea.
And then he's too scared to get caught to share.
Ooh, I hate guys like that.
And why do boys with braces always want a french kiss?
Uh, pass me some more of that cookie dough.
Mmm.
I never knew you could eat it raw.
It's almost as good as ice cream.
You know they make ice cream with cookie dough already in it.
Damn sister get me my keys.
Lou Ann, where have you been?
We were supposed to be crying all night.
I spent the whole day with Uncle Hank.
Lou Ann, why don't you go get the fold out ready?
OK.
Good night, Uncle Hank and Aunt Peggy.
Good night, Hank.
What did you do?
I did what you couldn't do.
Now, I'm not saying you're not good at what you do.
I'm just saying I'm better.
I went in there and fixed her like fixing a carburetor.
And you know what?
It was fun, like fixing a carburetor.
But Hank, I told you not to meddle.
This is a natural process and you cannot manipulate... You know, you look pretty.
Really?
Oh, Hank.
Well, that's sweet.
But I mean it, you have got to stop... You look pretty, Peg.
Oh, thank you.
You ladies go on ahead.
We gotta help Bill close his jeans.
All right, let's go.
All right, we have to find a nice boyfriend for Lou Ann.
Boy, that seems like a pile of work just to get your den back.
Well, it's not about my den.
It's about that poor girl living in my den.
So what's your type?
Uh, never mind about her type.
Just find a regular guy.
It's a scientific fact that women like round muscular butts.
I'm gonna look for a guy with a round muscular butt.
Uh, maybe we should split up.
Oh, one more thing.
Peggy doesn't know about this.
Oh, you want me to tell her?
No, Bill.
Just dance with her.
Keep her busy.
What, me?
Dancing?
I don't know, I don't know.
My arms around a warm, okay.
Hmm.
Nah.
Possible.
Dale, I bought you a beer.
Mind if I dance with your wife?
Take her.
Sucker.
Y'all know, man, he ain't gonna have to worry about that.
If you go out and dance, she's gonna go Dutch, man.
Something to know of the way.
Well, you smell nice.
Dance with me, sugar?
Hey, boy, take what, man?
That ain't over CK1, man.
It's like catnip.
Hey, you seem like a regular guy.
Hi, what's Hank doing over there?
Well, I don't see him.
Bill, why are you spinning me into souvenir gold?
Been a while, I can't remember all the steps.
Well, just do what I say and we'll get along fine.
On three, brush, wrap and fan, lift and scoop, scrape and scoop.
What's your name, son?
Wade, sir.
That's some buckle you got there.
Thank you, sir.
It means a lot coming from a man like you who, I can plainly see, knows a thing or two about buckles.
Well, uh, well, this round's on me.
Fangeric by left.
Hitch right.
Fan fan, double dog down.
Hitch kick now, select that heel.
Heel toe, heel toe, heel toe, knee toe heel.
Quarterback, huh?
Varsity.
Love your mama?
You know I do.
She cook with a gas range?
Propane.
I don't know if I'm ready, Uncle Hank.
Sure you are.
And Wade's a catch-and-a-half.
He can run the 40 in under five seconds.
But my heart is telling me that... Your heart is telling you who's the boss.
You or your heart.
You are.
Your heart is your employee.
So get your heart off its butt and back to work.
You're right, Uncle Hank.
What am I waiting for?
Let's go get weighed.
Bill, you need to have more confidence in yourself.
If you ask Peggy Hill, you boot scoot with the best of them.
Well, I don't know.
All right, this next one's going to be ladies' choice.
Excuse me, Bill.
Hey, Peggy.
Better than aerobics, huh?
You worked up quite a sweat.
That's not my sweat.
Where's Luan?
Luan's fine.
She's gonna get her eye at home with a friend.
Tush, push on three.
And three.
Is Luan gonna marry her new boyfriend?
Well, you never can tell, but my guess is, yeah.
Luan!
That's buckly.
Those better be for me.
No, they're for me for later.
Where's Luanne?
Luanne is out with her new boyfriend.
She's in love.
You blew it, Dip Head.
You can't compete with this new guy.
He's a football player, and football players know how to treat women right.
Now get off my lawn and don't come back.
Why'd you send Buckley away?
Luann wants him back.
Not gonna happen.
I found her a new guy.
You broke the rebound rule?
What has gotten into you, Hank?
Well, I was kind of hoping she might fall in love with Wade.
Well, hoping one hand and booing the other, see which one gets full first.
Mm-mm, you are out of your depth, Hank Hill.
You've opened a Pandora's box.
A box that has a sign that reads, For Women Only.
As long as it took that river to carve the Grand Canyon, that is how long women have been learning to subtly manipulate relationships.
You only think it's easy because we make it look easy.
Did you really believe you could step in and fix it overnight?
Could you really be such a fool?
Who is you, Hank Hill?
Who is you?
No, no!
No, everything's gonna be fine.
Wade's a good guy.
You don't know.
He runs fast.
It'll be fine.
What's that?
See?
Everything's fine.
Good ol' Wade drove her home.
Look at that, he's fixed his dodge up just like Boom Hours.
Well, why on earth would anyone do that?
Boom Hours?
Good night.
Thanks for the lift.
No!
Luanne, what happened to Wade?
Why aren't you with Wade?
I want Wade.
As soon as you left, Wade turned into Mr. Grabby Sam.
I think that you just fixed me up with him so you could get your den back.
Thank goodness, Boomhower gave me a lift.
A lift?
Is that what they're calling it these days?
You can't trust this guy.
He's a no-good, immoral, skirt-chasing rascal.
So, at least you like him better than Buckley.
What are you saying?
He's your new boyfriend?
Hank, so what if he is?
If he is, he ain't no more.
Hank, you can't tell me what to do.
You're not my father.
Yeah, I guess not.
Damn straight I'm not.
But while you're under my roof, I'm your landlord.
And as your landlord, I forbid you to date Boomhauer.
Shut up, Hank.
I can find another roof.
I'll stay at Boom Howers!
Fine!
Wait, man, I'll just stay there and go work out, man.
Those little girls come around here, they just flat-out know, man.
Thanks, Boom Howers.
Let's go.
Dang old women from Mars, man.
I'll tell you what.
Don't go in there, Lou Ann.
I'm warning you.
You'll be sorry.
Damn it, this neighborhood is turning into Melrose Place.
Hank, it is after midnight.
What the heck are you doing?
Clearing some space from a leaf blower.
Mm-hmm.
Now, Hank, this is not about the leaf blower, is it?
Sure it is.
What are you eating?
Nothing.
You are eating your emotions, aren't you?
Maybe who knows?
I don't know.
I don't care, whatever.
You thought you could fix Lou Ann like a flywheel drive plate, but a flywheel drive plate doesn't talk back.
Flywheel drive plates do not have feelings.
Flywheel drive plates... I took her in, Peg.
I put a 20-year roof over her head and a sofa sleeper under the rest of her.
And this is the thanks I get?
Well, no thanks.
Just face it, Hank Hill.
The only reason you're this upset is because you care so much about Luanne.
The only thing I care about is getting my den back.
Boy, I've never been in here before.
Oh, it sure is bachelor-y.
Can I turn this light on?
Oh, uh, that's real pretty.
Uh, gosh.
Oh, you move very fast, boomhauer.
I'm having all these feelings and I need just a little time to... Okay, last case of beer.
Let's divvy it up.
Hey, it don't split up even anymore.
That one's Boom Howard's.
That cradle robber's getting none of my beer.
Boom Howard didn't do anything.
And even if he did, why do you care?
Lu Ann's not your relation.
Hell, she's my wife's brother's daughter.
You can't get any closer than that.
Look, let's just split that six pack up.
We can each take two.
Tell you what, why don't I just take the whole thing?
Okay, Mom.
Let's try and move a mile.
and split kick right and back and split kick left and sideways shuffle go!
Oh, are you okay, Bobby?
Yeah.
Well, it was a nice move.
Aw, honey.
It's just not right without Luan.
Yeah.
This was a nice idea, Pig.
Get us out of that house.
Son, they got eight kinds of ketchup here, and three kinds of ketchup.
Not that I'm going to have some of that fried chicken, fried plate, fried chicken, fried side, fried, fried okra.
Luan!
And boomhauer too.
Well, isn't this a nice surprise?
Uh, is that gravy lumpy tonight?
Hey, I'm Peggy, Uncle Hank.
I'll take a bowl of the white gravy and a bowl of brown gravy.
Hey, Dad, it's Luann, right behind you.
Dad, it's Luann.
Hey, Dad, can't you hear me?
Luann, right behind you.
Say, Hank, man, I don't know what you're thinking, man, but y'all got no man.
I ain't no dang old Woody Allen with that little soon lead, man.
This ain't nothing going to happen.
Boom, Hauer, you're not going to talk your way out of this one.
Uncle Hank?
Don't uncle me anymore, Lou Ann.
Just come on by tomorrow and pick your stuff up.
I got it all boxed and ready to go.
Well, you finally got your wish.
You are going to get your den back.
I hope you're happy.
Look at she's crying again.
I guess she just got dumped by her new boyfriend, Boomhauer.
Boomhauer didn't dump her.
You did.
What?
What was that?
She said Boomhauer didn't dump her.
You did.
Pass the kids up.
I came for my stuff.
That's all in there.
I was moving stuff around and it seems that the room looks a little better this way.
The bed is keeping out.
Well, I figure there's no sense in packing it up night after night.
Love you, Uncle Hank.
Oh, Lord.
See, still looking?
Yep.
You know, Hank, maybe it's time to settle this.
Yeah, I just hate these big emotional scenes.
Well, let's get it over with.
Boom hour!
Yep.
Beer?
That was beautiful.