Hey, look at that.
Well, I guess we're finally getting some new neighbors.
I tell you, if that boy handles the football half as good as he handles the cardboard box, Arlen High's got herself a new tight end.
Hey, you think the dad's a good bowler?
Yeah, he looks like a good bowler.
Maybe he needs someone to bowl with.
Notice how he lifts with his legs.
I think they're gonna fit in just fine.
Howdy fellas.
What brings you to Ireland?
Well, uh, this family hired us to move their stuff.
Well, I'll be damned.
They look Japanese.
Nope.
I think they're Chinese.
How can you tell?
Japanese guys usually have glasses and a suit and a tie and stuff like that.
Uh-huh.
Well, a neighbor's a neighbor.
Let's go over and say hi.
You reckon they even speak English?
Yeah, man, them Chinese, man.
You can't understand a word they say, man.
They just try to listen to the whole upside down whatnot.
Hi there, I'm Hank Hill.
I live next door, which means I'm your neighbor and you're my friend.
I think you'll find we have a great little community here.
What do you think of it so far?
I am Khan, Super Newsome Bone.
Hmm, so that's pronounced... Khan, right?
Nice to meet you.
What the hell are you trying to do?
So are you Chinese or Japanese?
I lived in California last 20 years, but first come from Laos.
Huh?
Laos.
We lay ocean.
The ocean?
What ocean?
We all lay ocean!
From Laos, stupid!
It's a landlocked country in Southeast Asia.
It's between Vietnam and Thailand, okay?
Population, 4.7 million.
So are you Chinese or Japanese?
That is so very exciting.
It's like we get to travel to the Orient without having to worry about diarrhea or being jailed for our pro-democracy beliefs.
You know, at the beauty academy, they teach us that people aren't black or white or yellow or red, but their hair can be.
I'm going to invite our new neighbors to dinner.
We can't expect them to break the eyes.
These people are by nature shy and reserved.
I read somewhere that the Chinese language has 72 words for us, but no word for friend.
Howdy, you all.
Howdy, howdy, howdy.
Yeah.
Can you believe this crap?
You want to live in this country, learn to speak English.
I'm not going.
But you promise.
Why go?
I could just stay home, order a bucket of chicken and watch Hee-Haw.
Same thing.
Khan, please, for once, try not to piss off neighbor.
We kick out of Laos.
We kick out of Anaheim.
I'm tired of running.
Hello, Khan.
Oh, damn.
Damn.
Oh, you have damn fine house.
Lead-free since 1988.
This is my wife, Meen, and daughter, Con Junior.
And this is Peggy Hill.
On behalf of Arlen, Texas, I would like to welcome you to our country.
Now, please make yourselves at home and take off your shoes.
Wait.
You just shampoo carpet?
Come on, Bobby.
Have some seconds.
The girl's lapping you.
I've never had beef chop suey before.
Really?
Oh, you poor dear.
You know, I read somewhere that in certain parts of China, meat is as scarce as toilet paper.
Well, where you read that?
Oh, who can remember?
You know, as a substitute teacher, I have to review all sorts of learning materials.
My beat was on a placement.
So you're a teacher?
Maybe you can tell me why art and test scores are so low.
I know why.
It's because Khan Junior not there to bring up average.
You know, my boy here might not be the best test taker, but he's got near perfect attendance.
Tell him, Bobby.
I hope you all save some room for my famous apple brown Betty.
The recipe is a closely guarded family secret.
Passed on from my mother's mother to my mother to me.
And someday, I will give it to my Bobby.
Well, at least the brown Betty was good.
You must give me recipe.
Oh, man, you know I can't do that.
But what I can do is offer you some leftovers.
Here, now just reheat this for 10 minutes.
I have already said way too much.
Well, y'all come back now, you hear?
That's Texan for Sayonara.
Oh my, Peggy here.
What big feet you have, like boat.
Well, that's just the way God made me.
Hey, look at me!
I'm like little girl in mama's shoes!
Okay, bye-bye now, bye-bye!
Now, honey, she didn't mean anything, bud.
You do not come into a woman's home and insult her fate.
You just don't.
Oh, come on, Peg.
Remember when you first moved here from Montana?
He called Pops so depop.
And you thought 93 in the shade was hot.
Our new neighbors are just like you.
All they need is a little bit of time and Hank Hill to watch out for them.
Well, do you think my feet are too big?
No, there's just more of you to love.
Ow.
Sorry.
Be careful, Bobby.
That's one of them Chinese fighting dogs.
Oh, it's a West Highland Terrier.
Yeah, that's it.
So what's his name?
Doggy.
Yes, Con Junior, he's a doggy.
Now, can you tell me his name?
He's called Doggy.
And that's called a doggy too, but her name is Lady Bird.
She's a purebred Georgia bloodhound.
Her momma tracked down James Earl Wraith.
Yeah!
Uh, aren't kids great?
They're too young to know about fear or prejudice.
They won't have to learn that till high school.
Yep, there's a real lesson here for all of us.
Move, please.
You're standing on my hose.
Dad, look, Lady Bird and Doggy like each other.
Of course they do, son.
They're neighbors.
You know, Con, I just found a breeding partner for my Lady Bird.
If you're interested in having a real American dog, I can give... What the hell?
Get him off!
Get him off of her!
Your Lady Bird!
She's real slut!
Lady Bird is not a slut.
She is in heat.
Her hormones have overwhelmed her natural modesty.
For Pete's sake, would you tie up your dog?
You tie your dog?
She seduced my doggy.
That's ridiculous.
Lady Bird can only love another purebred Georgia bloodhound.
You know what I think, Hank Hill?
I think you a narrow-minded redneck.
Oh, I get it.
Just because I'm from Texas, I gotta be some kind of redneck.
Chinese and their stupid stereotypes.
Get out my property!
Sorry, Lady Bird.
I know you didn't mean to, uh, have relations with that dog, but I gotta tie you up anyway, if only to protect your virtue and good name.
Well, hey, look there.
Maybe Con will let you borrow his sexy little import.
I'd cut my entire quarter acre with the lady bick before I'd borrow that man's mower.
I just don't like him.
Why?
Because he's Chinese?
No.
It's always great.
What the hell's the difference?
I don't like the man.
That has nothing to do with where he's from.
I'm no redneck.
He could be from Mars for all I care.
Believe me, Hank, if Con were from Mars, you'd care.
Especially after he's stolen every last drop of earth's drinkable water to transport back to his home planet.
Mars.
Come up, stop dawdling the wind.
We've got to pick up that pizza before the cheese gets cold and the pineapple gets hot.
What's the rush?
If we're not there in 30 minutes, it's free.
Peggy here!
Wait, Peggy, it's me.
Stop.
Oh, my man.
I almost did not see you there.
Peggy here.
I feel deeply, deeply sorry about dinner.
We get off to bad start.
I see things I should only have thought.
Oh, Min.
Thank you.
I mean, it must have taken a lot of courage to apologize like that.
And I know.
I was once the new girl in town myself.
Me?
Khan?
Khan Junior have a barbecue tomorrow.
It means so much if you come.
Well, thank you, Min.
We would be honored to come.
And if you need any help with the barbecue, or if you just want to know what a barbecue is, you give me a call.
Uh-uh, Peggy.
I can't go.
I won't.
Not after what he said about Lady Bird.
Oh, Hank, come on.
Now, Min and I just made up.
We have to go.
And if you stay home, people will think you don't like Conn just because he's Oriental.
That is ridiculous.
I hate the man because he's rude and nasty.
Not because of what his people did to us in WW2.
Well, Hank, I know that.
But everyone else, they'll say Hank Hill is a racist.
What the hell kind of country is this where I can only hate a man if he's white?
Hank Hill, you will go to that party, you will pretend to like con, and you will drink until you actually do.
Go on.
Uh, howdy, Conn.
Howdy, howdy, howdy.
Here you go.
I thought you might enjoy 7.5 gallons of pure premium propane.
Are you kidding?
No, I cook with mesquite.
Give meat a nice taste of wood.
And I cook with propane.
Gives meat a nice taste of meat.
Thank you.
Hey, whatever.
Some cultures like mesquite, some prefer propane.
Doesn't mean we can't all get along.
Just because I happen to sell propane and propane accessories... Okay, all right.
Go stick tank on the table.
Keep napkins from blowing away.
Con, super news upon.
Ah, okay.
You honor me by giving me gas.
Doggy's just like me.
He's new in town and he's only got one friend.
But at least you're not tied up.
If I were, I'd just dislocate my shoulders and slip out of the knot.
I'd chew through the leash.
I bet it tastes just like a Bible cover.
Hey, let's untie them.
They belong together.
And it's fun to watch them play piggyback.
There you go, boy.
Go play with Lady Bird.
Be with your true love.
Wait!
Come back!
You're in love!
Oh look, it's Piggy here, my new best friend!
She's so pretty in her little yellow sundress.
Oh man, you are so sweet.
I could just mix you up in some jello and eat you for dessert.
Oh Piggy here, look at husbands.
Too bad men don't get along like we do.
We get along?
Man, stupid.
Women's smart mm-hmm the whole world over hey Peggy here.
Look what I make Peggy here brown Betty.
Oh, but that's impossible.
I never gave you the oh Where'd you get my granny's recipe?
I figured out myself and then make it better her recipe missing one thing Flavor I thank your Pete.
I add flavor not make flavor now tastes much better.
Don't you think Peggy here?
Please try a Piggy Brown Betty.
Would you like a Piggy Brown Betty?
It's tasty.
Delicious.
While Piggy, to be honest, I have always had trouble keeping your brown Betty down, but this here is pure heaven.
Those burgers look pretty done to me.
Not yet.
You might want to turn them now.
Too soon.
Okay.
Uh... Whoa.
You might want to turn them now.
No.
Please go away.
Please, Con, you're burning them.
That's too much char.
Shut mouth and open mouth.
Oh.
Hmm.
Boy, howdy.
That is the best damn burger I ever ate.
Stop, stop pushing.
That's enough for everyone.
If three of you go home right now, ha ha ha.
Joke.
Doggy.
Con Junior?
Yeah?
Why are you named Con Junior?
My father wanted a boy.
Yeah, so did mine.
My dad is so lame.
He makes me practice violin five hours a day.
My dad won't let me watch TV more than five hours a day.
Well, my dad's making me memorize 2,000 words for the SAT.
He's such an autocrat.
What's a SAT?
I tell you, Peggy, there's nothing these people can't make better.
First the automobile, then the color TV, and now the hamburger.
How do they do it?
With a dash of nutmeg, Hank.
A dash of nutmeg.
Oh, Peggy here!
Your husband likes burgers so much, I give you a recipe.
Now you can please him.
I don't care what country he's from, any man who can make a burger like that is okay by me.
Oh, you said it.
Boy, it was so good, it's almost a shame to lose it to the process of digestion.
Yeah, man, I'll tell you what, the dang old onion soup powder, man.
Just put that little bit old ab you don't need old grilled onions, man.
How about you, Dale?
How many you got under your belt?
Zero.
Huh?
How come?
Don't eat dog.
Okay.
Here are the facts as I see them.
Khan served your dog.
Khan did not serve us dog.
That's just an awful stereotype.
Chinese people don't really do that.
Well, I don't know.
Anyone crazy enough to put nutmeg in brown Betty?
Well, they'd be crazy enough to do anything.
Hey, even if they did feed us dog, you know, who are we?
Who are we to judge other cultures?
You know, maybe they're on to something.
They did invent paper, you know.
Quit talking like that.
Dog is man's best friend.
You wouldn't eat your best friend, would you?
Of course not.
Wait, are we talking about some kind of lifeboat situation here?
Because I don't want to paint myself into a corner.
Look, I can settle this right now.
That woman gave us a recipe.
See?
Right here.
It says chopped meat, not chopped dog.
Dog is meat.
Mm.
You said it, friend.
Oh.
I was just trying to get that awful taste off my fingers.
Doggy?
Hello?
Dog pound?
Yes, hello?
I'm looking for dog.
Sweet, sweet dog.
Have big barbecue today and dog run out.
All about 20, 25 pound.
Good lord, it's true.
Oh, I'll call you back.
Hey, Kill.
What a nice surprise.
Hey, Khan, come quick.
Your best friend is here.
Oh, no.
Uh, that's OK.
What are you doing here?
I can't hear you over my weed, Parker.
Hey, where you going, kiddo?
Stop!
I can't hear you.
My good tentamom!
What you doing?
You ruined my yard!
You crazy redneck!
That's a niff!
We're never gonna find Doggie.
I know.
Wanna ride bikes?
Hey, Lady Bird's a bloodhound.
Maybe she can find Doggie.
Yeah!
Come on, Lady Bird.
Lead us to Doggie.
My God, Dale, you were right.
Their dog is gone.
All gone.
I caught men on the phone with some kind of doggy butcher.
She was placing an order.
This is very dangerous.
They know that you know.
And now they gotta come after you.
They do?
Yep.
They'll probably get you with a blow dart.
That's their way.
But you'll just think it's a mosquito bite.
Until you die, then you'll know the truth.
Why?
Why would they shoot people?
Human meat's tough, flavorless.
They should be out hunting for more dog.
Good God!
He's got Lady Bird!
It's still wet.
Maybe there's time.
Come on guys, we gotta save Lady Bird.
Gah!
I've been hit!
Quick!
Somebody suck out the poison!
Oh no!
Lady Bird!
Whoa.
That psycho Redneck is back.
Why, he's so mad.
You do something wrong?
You're the one who insulted his propane.
You're the one who made fun of Peggy Hill's monster feet.
Open up, Con.
Open up now.
Get my bat.
I know you're in there.
Go away.
I do nothing wrong.
Look, Con, I understand that life is valued differently in your part of the world, largely as a result of overcrowding and famine.
But you're in my country now.
You're a crazy man.
I call the police.
If anyone's going to be calling the police, it's going to be me.
Police?
What do you want from me?
I want my lady bird.
You understand me?
Give me my dog back or else.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Tough guy.
I'm so scared.
You want a piece of this?
Dad, no!
It's all our fault.
We lost the dogs.
They wanted to play with each other, so we untied them, and they ran away, and now we can't find them.
You what?
You mean you...
The, the dogs, they're still alive?
What do you think happened?
Well, I, uh, nothing.
We're sorry, Dad.
We looked everywhere.
We really did.
Bobby, you really screwed up this time.
Con, Junior, you fought in with a bad crowd.
You made me fight with my neighbor.
You made the neighbor man crazy.
Go to your room!
What, you say, go to your room?
I say, go to your room.
You spank?
No, sir.
Don't believe in it.
No, me neither.
I think it barbaric.
How about bed without dessert?
Never fail.
Huh.
Wouldn't figure a child could be motivated by a fortune cookie and an orange slice.
Oh, the cookie may be small, but it contains great wisdom.
And orange is sweet and juicy.
You know, Con, we may deny our kids completely different desserts, but they both go to bed hungry.
And that's what really matters.
Well, I guess we're not so different after all.
Boy, howdy.
Woo!
Welcome to the neighborhood, con su panusan pon.
Just call me con.
I don't got all damn day.
I'm running out of time.
Give me the antidote, man.
This is my granny's five alarm jambalaya.
You want less hot, more spicy, add nutmeg.
Less hot, more spicy, add nutmeg, of course.
Okay.
Aunt Laverne's chicken fried chicken.
Too much Mrs. Dash, add nutmeg.
And this here is my very own rabbit stew.
Rabbit?
You rednecks will eat anything.